(Leonard:)There are a couple of
things I did with Penny
(Leonard:)that might be a
little silly, but...
(Raj:)Like what?
(Leonard:)Every once in a while,
before we'd go to bed,
(Leonard:)I'd put on a little show
for her.
(Raj:)What do you mean
"a show"?
(Leonard:)Well, you know,
the way I took my clothes off.
(Raj:)Like, to music?
(Leonard:)I'd look pretty stupid
if there was no music.
(Raj:)So you'd do
a striptease?
(Leonard:)I wasn't swinging
around a pole.
(Raj:)Good, good.
(Leonard:)There was one time
I put body glitter on.
(Raj:)Well, I don't think
you have to worry
(Raj:)about Penny telling
my sister that.
(Leonard:)No, she wouldn't.
(Raj:)Your big problem
is me telling her.
(Leonard:)You really are
a mean little man.
(Priya:)Oh, God, that's so true.